{
    "subject": "resource/Napoleon_Solo",
    "predicate": "ontology/portrayer",
    "object": "resource/Robert_Vaughn",
    "human_readable": "Napoleon Solo was portrayed by Robert Vaughn.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9312939643859863,
            "question": "Who portrayed Napoleon Solo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8910926580429077,
            "question": "Who else might have played Napoleon Solo if Robert Vaughn hadn't taken the role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8758264780044556,
            "question": "What impact did Robert Vaughn's portrayal of Napoleon Solo have on popular culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.671818196773529,
            "question": "What character was Robert Vaughn known for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46675559878349304,
            "question": "Is Robert Vaughn a famous actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4535112679004669,
            "question": "Was Robert Vaughn involved in other famous productions besides this role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42675015330314636,
            "question": "What genre was the show featuring Napoleon Solo likely in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3545628488063812,
            "question": "What time period was the show featuring Napoleon Solo probably set in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33650118112564087,
            "question": "Can you name a TV show featuring Napoleon Solo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24564802646636963,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of a spy character like Napoleon Solo?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Napoleon Solo was portrayed by Robert Vaughn.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8546_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a TV show featuring Napoleon Solo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8546_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What time period was the show featuring Napoleon Solo probably set in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8546_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre was the show featuring Napoleon Solo likely in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8546_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8546_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8546_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8546_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8546_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8546_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8546_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8546_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8546_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8546_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8546_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The text states that Napoleon Solo was portrayed by Robert Vaughn in Seasons 1, 2, 3 and 4 of The Man from U.N.C.L.E. and episode 3 of The Girl from U.N.C.L.E.. Additionally, it is mentioned that Robert Vaughn played secret agent Napoleon Solo on the 1960s spy comedy series, which further confirms the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Napoleon Solo was portrayed by Robert Vaughn\" multiple times, thus supporting the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}